Finding Aid for the Oliver Eckhardt Players Records LSC.0981
UCLA Library Special Collections
Oliver Eckhardt Players records
circa 1915
UCLA Library Special Collections
Oliver Eckhardt Players
LSC.0981
2.5 Linear Feet (5 boxes)
The Oliver Eckhardt Players were a repertory company, producing such plays as Alias Jimmy Valentine, Get-Rich-Quick-Wallingford, and The Girl of the Golden West. The collection consists of scripts for plays produced by the Oliver Eckhardt Players.
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Provenance unknown.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9942335243606533
Biography
The Oliver Eckhardt Players were a repertory company, producing such plays as Alias Jimmy Valentine, Get-Rich-Quick-Wallingford, and The Girl of the Golden West.
Scope and Content
Collection consists of scripts for plays produced by the Oliver Eckhardt Players.
Theatrical companies -- Archives.; Scripts (documents).; Oliver Eckhardt Players -- Archives
- Alias Jimmy Valentine, c. 1915 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- The Big Idea by A.E. Thomas and Clayton Hamilton, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Cameo Kirby, c. 1915 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Facing the Music by James Henry Darnley, c. 1915 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- The Game, c. 1915 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Get-Rich-Quick-Wallingford, c. 1915 (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
- The Girl in the Taxi, c. 1915 (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
- The Girl of the Golden West, c. 1915 (Box 2, Folder 5-6)
- A Bachelor's Romance, c. 1915 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Boss of Z Ranch, c. 1915 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Brown's in Town, c. 1915 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- The Gamblers, c. 1915 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Gilded Fool, c. 1915 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- The Gold Mine, c. 1915 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- The Grafters, c. 1915 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- The House of a Thousand Candles, c. 1915 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- The House of Glass, c. 1915 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Kindling, c. 1915 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Miss Hobbs, c. 1915 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Lend Me Five Shillings, c. 1915 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- The Second in Command, c. 1915 (Box 5, Folder 4)